# ROBERT ISHOKA

# Software Engineer



# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

A software engineer student with 3 years of experience in building mobile applications, to solve problems that delight end-users.

Motivated to learn from senior engineers in an environment that values personal growth.

My focus is on building accessible & performant interfaces, for a variety of clients.



## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN**

MyBetaRide LTD, 7 Olufunmilola Okikiolu St, Ojodu Ikeja January 2022-April 2022

- Joint Development of the Riders mobile app using Flutter.
- Made and consumed REST APIs, made with (Node.js) Express.
- Published App to Google Play store.

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN**

CreditSwitch LTD, Ikeja GRA Lagos, March 2020-August 2020

- Developed webhooks and APIs to interface with the company's WhatsApp bot.
- Worked with the development team to refine some part of the company's mobile app.
- Tested various APIs using POSTMAN to check the functionality, reliability and performance of the programming interface.
- Fixed bugs in existing app.
- Implemented a new process, for a conversational experience with a WhatsApp chatbot.



## 

Email: ishokarobertt@gmail.com

Phone:

07011754596

Address:

2 Reggie Close Abule-Egba Lagos State.

GitHub:

https://github.com/Bert1041



# SOFT SKILLS

Adaptability

Strong Work Ethic

**Ouick Learner** 

Flexibility



## HARD SKILLS

Kotlin

JavaScript

PHP

Dart



### **EDUCATION**

#### **B.S. / COMPUTER SCIENCE**

University of Ibadan, Ibadan **Bachelor** in Computer Science.

2018-Current